{"test_questions": [[{"question": "How many JDBC driver types does Sun define?", "opta": "One", "optb": "Two", "optc": "Three", "optd": "Four", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Where is metadata stored in MySQL?", "opta": "In the MySQL database metadata", "optb": "In the MySQL database metasql", "optc": "In the MySQL database mysql", "optd": "None of the above is correct.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Who invented Java?", "opta": "Netscape", "optb": "Microsoft", "optc": "Sun", "optd": "None of the above is correct.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "To run a compiled Java program, the machine must have what loaded and running?", "opta": "Java virtual machine", "optb": "Java compiler", "optc": "Java bytecode", "optd": "A Web browser", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which JDBC driver Type(s) can be used in either applet or servlet code?", "opta": "Both Type 1 and Type 2", "optb": "Both Type 1 and Type 3", "optc": "Both Type 3 and Type 4", "optd": "Type 4 only", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "________ is an open source DBMS product that runs on UNIX, Linux and Windows.", "opta": "MySQL", "optb": "JSP/SQL", "optc": "JDBC/SQL", "optd": "Sun ACCESS", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is sent to the user via HTTP, invoked using the HTTP protocol on the user's computer, and run on the user's computer as an application?", "opta": "A Java application", "optb": "A Java applet", "optc": "A Java servlet", "optd": "None of the above is correct.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What MySQL property is used to create a surrogate key in MySQL?", "opta": "UNIQUE", "optb": "SEQUENCE", "optc": "AUTO_INCREMENT", "optd": "None of the above -- Surrogate keys are not implemented in MySQL.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is not true of a Java bean?", "opta": "There are no public instance variables.", "optb": "All persistent values are accessed using getxxx and setxxx methods.", "optc": "It may have many constructors as necessary.", "optd": "All of the above are true of a Java bean.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A JSP is transformed into a(n):", "opta": "Java applet.", "optb": "Java servlet.", "optc": "Either 1 or 2 above.", "optd": "Neither 1 nor 2 above.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which JDBC driver Type(s) can you use in a three-tier architecture and if the Web server and the DBMS are running on the same machine?", "opta": "Type 1 only", "optb": "Type 2 only", "optc": "Both Type 3 and Type 4", "optd": "All of Type 1, Type 2, Type 3 and Type 4", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What programming language(s) or scripting language(s) does Java Server Pages (JSP) support?", "opta": "VBScript only", "optb": "Jscript only", "optc": "Java only", "optd": "All of the above are supported", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What servlet processor was developed by Apache Foundation and Sun?", "opta": "Apache Tomcat", "optb": "Apache Web server", "optc": "Sun servlet processor", "optd": "None of the above is correct.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is bytecode?", "opta": "Machine-specific code", "optb": "Java code", "optc": "Machine-independent code", "optd": "None of the above is correct.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is invoked via HTTP on the Web server computer when it responds to requests from a user's Web browser?", "opta": "A Java application", "optb": "A Java applet", "optc": "A Java servlet", "optd": "None of the above is correct.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which JDBC driver Type(s) is(are) the JDBC-ODBC bridge?", "opta": "Type 1", "optb": "Type 2", "optc": "Type 3", "optd": "Type 4", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "How many copies of a JSP page can be in memory at a time?", "opta": "One", "optb": "Two", "optc": "Three", "optd": "Unlimited", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which JDBC driver Types are for use over communications networks?", "opta": "Type 3 only", "optb": "Type 4 only", "optc": "Both Type 3 and Type 4", "optd": "Neither Type 3 nor Type 4", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "JDBC stands for:", "opta": "Java Database Connectivity", "optb": "Java Database Components", "optc": "Java Database Control", "optd": "None of the above is correct.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "How does Tomcat execute a JSP?", "opta": "As a CGI script", "optb": "As an independent process", "optc": "By one of Tomcat's threads", "optd": "None of the above is correct.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}